// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Solve 300 - 150 x 2",
        answer: "0",
        options: [
            "300",
            "0",
            "50",
            "150"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What's the missing number in the sequence: 3, 6, 18, 72, _",
        answer: "360",
        options: [
            "216",
            "144",
            "360",
            "288"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How many prime numbers are there from 1 to 30",
        answer: "10",
        options: [
            "7",
            "10",
            "11",
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How many seconds are there in a week",
        answer: "604,800",
        options: [
            "604,800",
            "49,000",
            "144,000",
            "760,000"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "How many months are there in 120days, on average ?",
        answer: "4months",
        options: [
            "5months",
            "4months",
            "3months",
            "6months"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Giving 9^(X) =  81. Find the value of X ? ",
        answer: "2",
        options: [
            "3",
            "2",
            "4",
            "9"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Evaluate 3(Y + 2) = 11, find the value of Y ?",
        answer: "3",
        options: [
            "2",
            "6",
            "4",
            "3"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "A right angle triangle has angles 32 and 128, what is the missing angle ?",
        answer: "20",
        options: [
            "200",
            "90",
            "20",
            "270"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the range of an Obtuse angle ?",
        answer: "Between 90 and 180",
        options: [
            "Between 0 and 180",
            "Between 90 and 180",
            "Between 90 and 360",
            "Between 0 and 90"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The peimeter round a circle ?",
        answer: "Circumference",
        options: [
            "Circumference",
            "Radius",
            "Volume",
            "Diameter"
        ]
    },
];